ALLYN CHRISTOPHER: Okay, our turbine's properly installed there as well as these bearings.
Look at that.
It's practically a perpetual motion machine.
I'll say it three times.
Turbine shaft shield.
Shaft shield.
There are just a couple of places where it goes here and we're going to put this on right here as a place holder and then we are going to take--yes, now the screws from this are going to be the originals too.
And again, low torque, low speed.
It should make that clicking sound.
But you're not going to hear the clicking sound 'cause I'm not tightening them all the way 'cause this has a--you can see over here, it's keyed, so that it can slide in and out and once we get the next piece on, we're going to set it at the perfect, perfect setting for it, look at that.
All right, here's our old one.
This is the turbine shield, the turbine itself, and still has the old tube attached and so again I'm going to turn it out.
Again, one of the pieces that doesn't come in the kit, very rarely does anything happen to this.
So, you're more likely to break it during a repair than you are to actually do it--for it break itself during operation.
Old tube, you see it's a little warped, stiff, doesn't want to retain, it's not good.
Good thing the kit comes with a brand new, flexible, very supple.